They said the gods were gone
But we build new ones in code and song
Every follower, a priest
Every troll, a test
We speak the truth
Seals on the Colts great door
One for
Hear the choir of lost accounts, their laughed accounts, their silenced mouths.
Each band of baptism meet, strike a scar.
Type your vows in holy code
Control out soul, the chosen mode
Log in beloved, take your role
For every cult begins with one
I don't think he was that good looking of a guy, but I think I'm better looking.
Hi.
How was everyone's day?
I had a nice nap.
My schedule is way off now.
So it was interesting, it's interesting to watch sometimes people's reactions to certain
things.
So I'm kind of looking for sometimes, but I'm doing a few things, hold on a second.
make some more music too. You know what? I'm allowed to play in my music. I'm not allowed to play
other music. Most music I'm not allowed to play, you know, most anybody else's, but I can play all
my own, so why not make it?
Hey, Rodimus Prime, I know, didn't she?
I mean, she really is.
I mean, it's like, the weird thing is that she has,
like there's like the other side of the personality
that is very, you know, it's very sweet, it's very kind.
And it's like, it's just funny how some people are so fooled.
But yeah, when you do get to know somebody and you
It's good when you can integrate both sides of it, but it's like really confusing when it's like there's two different
It's almost like two different people almost, right
Some people get the one version and some get the other and then it's like they kind of don't notice
The differences, right, but I won't I won't
You haven't? Well, it might not be real. It might be just that a mask that certain people see at certain times
I certainly did. I mean, I'm very
Not I'm not easily fooled. I'm very
Mmm, I react I kind of treat people like they treat me kind of and so
But I'll really notice it's a yeah. Yeah. Well, yeah, I'm
For the last year, I've noticed that that's I got the other personality the first
probably
First several months that I knew it didn't change and it hasn't gone back since I never I never
Unless I talked to her on the phone personally. I never saw the other side again
But first that's why it's like but personally
You know
When I did I was like, okay, that's the real
But maybe that was the mask right it's it's hard as hard
Because I want you know, I want to get along I'd love to
You don't think I tried I tried so hard and
I can get along perfectly well with other people, right?
Even if I, even if we fight and stuff like that,
it's like, there's an understanding.
It's not like the carrot and the stick
like I get with this jockey or whatever the fuck she is.
Hey, what's up, Mermaid?
How are you?
Good to see you.
Thanks for coming in.
Yeah, it was really weird yesterday.
There is at one point 50 people in the chat.
And no one was talking and that was like just uncomfortable, you know
Because it's like
And some people might think oh, those are fake or bots or something like that
I'm too cheap to
I'm too cheap to do that shit, but you know what so I don't know it's a it's weird
But hey, I'll always be honest and I'll always
Be at least real
Good, good to see you.
Like, my personality will only change.
Hey, K, how are you?
Good to see you.
My personality will only change towards you
if like, in reaction to like, how I'm treated.
And so, if I've blown up at her, there's reasons.
I mean, it's like, and maybe I look like that's the thing.
It's like, I can look like irrational
or some things sometimes.
But
That's why people sometimes miss the provocation
That's why she's I think so desperate not for me to play past clips
Yeah mermaids here kink gate and
NASCAR
Alois, are you new and they're gonna met you nice to meet you
Yeah, I bet you know, I it has gone on like long enough of like the I think I don't like how it's like
That's what I think that's all some people are here for is like to see me crashing out on her
Like that kind of drama really want to move past that because
It's just getting
Tiring tiring for me. So I'm gonna try to
Move on as much as I can. I
Do get emotionally
tethered and tangled sometimes and stuff
Yeah
And hey, I guess there's a say when you know, you know, right? I
It's like I like
The people that know I don't need to really explain it to you and the people that don't see it. I'll never
I'll never be able to it's like so it's like, you know
All I can do is be myself
So yeah, but we had it was a pretty good good night. I had
Alex got me a good a good dinner last night
Hot honey chicken sandwich, I think and a few coffees. I still have a I think it's still have a coffee, too
Okay, I'm frozen coffee, too. Well good. Um, oh my gosh, look at tricks
Oh
He is so funny
It's even it's even funnier that I can show I can't really pull the camera and you close it, but
His mouth is open and he's upside down
You're sleeping like there and there's Rudy sleeping right there
Okay, Rudy's right there Lenore and Lola
So they all have been really surrounding me lately look at them so funny moments surrounding me lately and
Think it's like that's my if anything that's my little circle of protection
Or I think my cats are very they're very sensitive to me like they and
They know when stuff is like raw. I it's like
When all that stuff was happening with like the you know the kind of harassment at the door and stuff like that
That was like the worst part is like they got really stressed out
I wasn't I didn't particularly get stressed out, but they don't like when people are at the door
They if they hear like little noise, they're very sensitive to that and it's like I don't like them being disturbed
And then it's like if I get annoyed
Yeah, so anyway
Yeah, but it yeah, so it is helpful when people talk though
It's like or ask questions or like make requests because it's going to the point where I mean I've
Probably streamed for thousand and thousand of hours. I'm told ever really every story
I can remember
I've
And so it's like at this point I need
To know what people want really
I can give it to them, but it's that I just don't and I just I don't want to waste anybody's time. I don't want to bore anybody
Yeah, sometimes yeah, so anyway, let's see
You got these cigars today
It's weird when the first thing I saw today though is um
One of the first posts I saw on YouTube said,
oh, try this new biscuit.
But it wasn't a biscuit.
It was like some kind of surveillance device.
I'm not hacking.
Weird.
I don't know.
It looks like a hockey puck.
The things that make you go hmm
So anyway
That's kind of fun this was funny about some things it's like
Some things will be like
There's something called doopers delight. Hey Kate. What have I been up to today? I mean I streamed until
Probably seven in the morning
And well
I had a good night of like, you know, I played some people's like conspiracy stuff. It's so interesting. I'm trying and I'm trying to make a presentation about this
Like, you know
The whole the word conspiracy is
It was pretty much created. I mean if you look at the word cons piracy, okay
That's interesting, but it's I think it was almost created as a discrediting
a word to discredit because once that word is brought up,
that's almost like, okay, well, the person's unhinged,
the person's paranoid, great.
And so it's like, that's a useful thing.
But here's what I also'm noticing is that,
like, it's really easy to hijack the emotional sense,
like, it's like, if you can infuse emotion into something
and make something like, you know,
Give people in their emotions about something their logic goes out the window. What happened? Okay, close the thing. Yeah, the logic goes out the window and
And I noticed it I don't know if it's because and I'm not a psychopath or anything like that, but I'm an Aquarius moon
You know anything about Aquarius moon. It's kind of like
I
Can look at some things without emotion. It's like for example
I'm not really affected by anyone's death unless I know of them, you know, personally if someone like so
It's like if they talk about a thousand people were killed or you know, or these people were killed this way
I know it doesn't I
Don't go into my mind and like picture like that there. I know it's like I can just I can be very
Hey chibi chibi, you know, it's covered. Yeah
News events TV dramas. No need to be involved. Yeah, I know. Yeah
The drama is really, it's a high burnout kind of thing.
And it's like, you can see it in a lot of the hosts.
It's like, and a lot of people will quit doing it
because they get burned out real quick about it.
But it gets tiring, right?
And it's like, cause there's just like,
you know, it's called the bullshit, right?
I can cover news events, blah, blah.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm gonna continue trying to create original content. I can always like play that stuff
But it's kind of funny it's because it's like there's such a resistance to like anything except the bullshit, right?
LGBTQ news. Yeah, I
Wish I was more connected. Well, I don't wish I'd say
I'm not particularly connected to the culture
in certain way, you know
but
So I don't know what I would cover. I I don't even like
as like I
Was kind of more into politics and that stuff and like the
you know
they're 20 years ago
but
During like they know like that look for example gay marriage
You know, like gay people used to not really like want to be
Like that was considered like a straight thing. Like that's like for straight people, right? And as and maybe I'm like more of the old school
mindset of that or it's like, I don't I don't need to be like the same as everybody else, right?
Yeah, I mean, yeah, you know, you so you get you get what I mean. Yeah
and
I
Think I mean and like also
I'm not promiscuous when I was when I was like 14 years old
I think I'm 1340 and I got a computer and I got on
Those chat rooms. I was and I was bad, you know, I was bad
Nowadays
It wouldn't be as acceptable as it was back then right
But yeah, I was I was bad
But not not truly promiscuous, but I was doing probably dangerous things like just meeting
meetings strange. Oh, yeah
But I got over that
and now I really I think I really want like I
Can't just have sex with I need to like
Think I think I need to be in love. I think that's like and I really haven't been so
You know, I don't really think about it. Let's see
Hmm
I'm sorry, I'm just squinting a little bit, okay.
Yeah, and also, unfortunately,
I'm kind of like stuck here a little bit.
I feel like I'm in like, I think I said,
I'm kind of in a purgatory or it's like,
I'm in a city, it's a pretty conservative city, right?
It's a nice city, really nice.
But it's not like I mean I'm here for my family pretty much
Yeah, I do have lots of time. I mean it's like and I do I mean I still I stream all the time I try different things
It's frustrating a little bit sometimes
For example when I'm not getting any feedback or
Or the feedback so negative when I know it's not like there's not really a reason for it
And it's like especially
For slander stuff that like a lot of people
believe
Like that makes me kind of mad about the state of human events and I don't like this so
Social stuff is not my my best
My best thing, you know
Has my blood sugar? No, no, why do you ask? I think it's pretty good. I can use the
I used them. I don't know. I don't have any I think this copy had no sugar in it. I
Don't have that. I don't have the beades though, right? Why must I Romulus? I don't know why they must
I don't I think that I am easy to project on to
I'm easy to demonize right
How's your blood sugar got it how's that how are you doing got it?
Yeah, and I oh my gosh, and do I think about my channel and stuff in my channel? Yes
It's like
Okay, so let's say I you know, I tell these fairy tales first of all. I'm not just telling the fairy tale. I'm I
rewrite them basically for adults, but I they were originally made for adults, right?
right
If you look at the original ones, they're very,
I mean, most people have figured this out.
They're like, they're very violent.
They, there's a, you can be very,
not, I wouldn't say they're for goodness' sake, really.
You know, in like the original Snow White, I guess,
they, at the end of it, they put the evil queen
in these hot shoes and make her dance to death.
I mean, that's a pretty crazy idea, right?
But even like the witch and handsome guy. This is a basically a cannibalism, right?
There's a really there was a really interesting thing that there is like this thing called the true story of Hansel and Gretel came out and
people really believed it
it's
turned out it was not true. It was but um
it was kind of creative
this story I'll tell you because uh, I
Thought it was kind of funny
In Germany in the woods hold on
Yeah, okay, so
So here's what it says. It says the story of Hansel and Gretel is believed to have roots in the great famine of 1314 to 1322
Which devastated Europe to your crop failures caused by climate change and volcanic activity
During this period of starvation led to extreme measures including childhood baminin fintas. I didn't even cannibalism
Okay, and so then it came out with something
Like the the realtors they could got even more more more
Specific than that I can find this thing it turned out that it was a recent thing
Louise Murphy, okay, I think it's by Louise Murphy. Oh, no, that's not it. Okay
But it is basically about
How the how the witch was like actually this baker and she had a recipe or something like that and Hansel and Gretel were actually these like went into
Steal the recipe and they killed her so they could steal the recipe for her strudel or something like that
It's a really it is a really funny story. Let me I wish I could find stuff easier like stuff to get so buried in the internet
Nowadays I'll just have strudel and see if I can okay
Yeah, okay, so this is from 1963. Okay
It says the witch that wasn't the real villain. Okay. I think this is the story. That's that's the uh, okay
Okay, so this is how a literary prank convinced Germany
that Hansel and Gretel was real.
It says, few fairy tales are as popular,
beloved as Hansel and Gretel, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, it was published in 1812.
It says, according to Dai Warheitlieber,
Hansel and Gretel, the truth about Hansel and Gretel,
the two siblings were in fact adult brother
and sister bakers,
living in Germany during the mid 17th century.
They murdered the witch in ingenious confectioner
in her own right to steal her secret recipe
And so, and it looked, and they made the book look like,
here's like the picture of the,
there's a picture of the gingerbread recipe.
They kind of made it look all a kind of authentic story.
Kind of interesting how I shared the screen.
Here's the actual page about it.
So here's the original gingerbread recipe that they stole, right?
It's archaeological artifact because so it says it caused it up for the media picked up the story and turned it into national news
Book of the week. No, it's because the year maybe the century. So they were got real excited about it
And there's a charred piece of the gingerbread found in the foundations of the house, right?
They found this piece of burnt gingerbread in that. I mean, okay
And I guess they had this guy look at this guy. I mean, I mean they went and they really investigated this
Well, they found parts they found the partially char remains the witch there is that
What is it this is crazy, I mean as I didn't know they had all this it's all this I think it's probably fake evidence
Let me see I'll read it
As intriguing as it might sound however, none of it proved to be true. In fact, the book turned out to be a literary forgery concocted by Hans Traxler, a German book author, blah, blah, blah.
But according to Dr. Claudia Schwab, a fairy tale researcher, the hoax with one of the bigger ones out there has done a very sophisticated level, right? Okay.
It says, in January 1945, Oseg evacuated together with the students to the small village of
Steinau or Straub in the German town of Hess.
There Oseg met a local farmer who referred to the nearby Spessart Woods as the Hexenwald
or the Witch's Forest, and whose grandfather had allegedly seen the witch's house inside
of it.
He went to investigate further, but with World War II he went to his hometown of Prague.
I've been to Prague.
It's in the Czech Republic.
But look, I always look for little things like this.
You see that little pyramid?
You see that?
I mean, it's like people will say,
oh, you're looking too much into that, blah, blah, blah.
Well, we know this is the fabricated oven.
Let's see, that's like a little sign.
I see that, and I've actually,
when you start looking for these things, you see them,
but maybe I'm just a little bit cuckoo.
So let's find the,
So this was a this was a real book I guess cannibalism and witchcraft. Okay, so let's see
The true story
See I need to yeah, I should probably prepare better for these
So there's not dead dead air, but hey, I like to find out things along with you guys so
Maybe it's here.
Okay.
The true story goes back to the cohort of tales
that originated in the Baltic regions.
There's a famine.
And I guess they did.
I mean, so there is some historical stuff.
I guess there was a famine and I guess parents did leave
their kids out in the woods and stuff like that
and that kind of stuff.
That's terrible.
There's other versions of it.
This is interesting the grimace of these tales is the Romanian story the little boy the wicked stepmother in this fairy tale two children are
Abandoned and find their way home following a trail of ashes
But when they return home the stepmother kills the little boy and forces the sister to prepare his corpse for a family meal
The horrified girl obeys but hides the boy's heart inside a tree.
The father unknowingly eats his son while the sister refuses to take part.
After the meal, the girl takes the brother's bones and puts them inside the tree with his heart.
The next day, a cuckoo bird emerges saying,
Cuckoo, my sister has cooked me, my father has eaten me, and now I am a cuckoo.
And say for my stepmother, the terrified stepmother throws a lump of salt at the bird,
but just falls back on her head, killing her instantaneously.
And the direct source for the story, as we know it, came from Henriette Dorothea Wilde,
the neighbor of the brother's grim, who narrated many of the tales.
And so, yeah, see, that doesn't even go into that, this particular, is this it?
I think I found a Wikipedia about it, yeah, here it is.
So, summary. According to the book, Osag determined that the fairy tale was based on the story of a 17th century baker named Hans Metzler and his sister Greta.
So, Hans and Greta, right? Hans and Greta Metzler lived in a village in the Spessart Forest during the Thirty Years' War and killed a woman named Katharina Schradian in order to steal her recipe for Nürnberger lebtkuchen, gingerbread.
In reality, Oseg did not exist, and the details were fabricated by Traxler.
Okay, and so, despite its fictional nature, the hoax convinced many Germans that time continues to have some traction.
In 1987, a one-hour, 22-minute movie, Oseg, or the war-heart Uber, Hansel and Gretel, loosely based on the novel, was released in Germany.
Okay.
I guess this is the Indie Man movie.
I want to I want to watch this movie, but look see they're like these adults
They're like the Hansel and Gretel or evil. I like how they turn things on their head sometimes, right?
So let me see if there's any one more thing I can find we'll search this one
Truth okay, maybe it's all I'm gonna be in German though. Oh, that's why it's good to translate
Truth
So that's the book I guess interesting
The documentary
Yeah, people would love to believe like all this stuff is true, you know, I do think that uh
Some of it's based on stuff but
This one's to the satire. I'll let this satire translate
Hmm
The look the trick is to make the work look like a serious scientific report
What helps are a few cleverly placed literature references at the end and above all many illustrations
There are 41 illustrations in the book, some of which are sketches and drawings,
others are actual photos that show him excavating, whatever, he found in the process.
So, it reminds me kind of of these tunnels. You know about the tunnels under the preschool?
They even had this FBI guy looking into these too. I'm sorry, this is how my mind works. It's
Let's watch this.
This is interesting.
Oh, shut up, Moshe.
Smack it, I'll smack you with that.
On King David, huh?
What, what?
Okay, I'm just kidding.
Okay, here, watch this.
This video is primarily about one aspect of the famous McMartin pre-school case.
The case began in 1984 from an accusation of sexual abuse of children perpetrated by the staff at the McMartin pre-school in Manhattan Beach, California.
That's the city next to me.
This ended up being the longest and most expensive trial ever.
Because of so many issues and aspects of this famous case, I am going to narrow it down to one issue, the question of were there tunnels below the school.
Here's some background. Some of the children reported that sexual abuse had taken place in tunnels and a secret room that were located underground below the school building.
The general consensus is that there were no such tunnels.
However, there are some people who still maintain that there is conclusive evidence
that there were tunnels and a secret room below the school
that had been filled in some time after the initial
investigation against the workers at preschool.
Now let's go over some things about research in general.
No matter what topic you research, even topics that don't have a trace of a publicly controversial
issue will yield conflicting information.
Not just minor discrepancies, but mutually exclusive contradictions in that if one is true
Then the other must be false and vice versa
If you research a topic and you do not come up with such contradictory
Information then I would say you haven't researched the topic thoroughly enough
Back to the books Buster
So how do we determine which information is correct?
The hard truth is that sometimes we really can't.
And sometimes you will see an author just throwing the towel and say something like,
there is conflicting information and we really don't know for sure which is correct.
I'll go over some tips that can help determine what information is more likely to be accurate.
One is the preponderance of information. If you find 10 sources that say X is true and only two sources that say Y is true,
X is more likely to be true. Look at the quality of the source.
You are more likely to get accurate information from a respected newspaper, magazine or scientific journal than you would from a tabloid or a TV talk show.
Does the source have a decidedly political or religious bias?
If so, the information is likely to be skewed.
Is it sensationalized?
If you read an article that starts out something like,
under the moonlit sky,
are two young explorers quietly crept into the dark forest,
armed only with flashlights
Yeah, if it reads like a novel it probably is one
Are there grammatical errors spelling mistakes internal inconsistencies?
Well, yeah, if the document has not been checked for basic errors
Then how likely is it that it has been checked for informational accuracy?
Parents of them were there or were there not tunnels below the McMartin school building
The first investigation into the matter was performed by parents of the
McMartin School's children in March of 1984. Halls were dug in the vacant lot
next to the school. They were looking for the remains of animals that had been
reported to be sacrificed and a secret underground room.
Days later, a professional archaeological firm that was hired by the district attorney's
office conducted an investigation of the site.
No tunnels, trap doors, or animal remains bearing any evidence of ritual sacrifice were discovered.
On April 21st, 1990, a second attempt by the parents was performed.
They dug a hole under the northeast corner of the school building to a depth of about 15 feet.
At this point, after finding no evidence of tunnels, some of these parents decided to hire a professional help.
Here are the key persons on this archaeological dig.
Crazy. Former FBI agent Ted Gunderson. He was also the boyfriend of one of the
McMartin parents, Jackie McGowley. I can't guarantee that pronunciation. Jerry
Hobbs, a professional gold miner and prospector, Don Michael, a geologist, and
Dr. Gary Stickel, an archaeologist from UCLA.
A month later, this team reported that they had discovered at least two tunnels that had been filled in.
Several newspapers reported the story, and Gunderson had appeared on television stating that filled-in tunnels had been found.
Dr. Stigl composed a report of his findings. A brief synopsis of the 186-page report is available online.
Stickel listed nine pre-established criteria that would have to be observed on the specific site,
which was the area directly below the McMartin School Building, in order to determine the existence of tunnels.
I'll go over the conclusions of these nine criteria.
Stickel concluded in his report that all of the criteria had been met,
and that conclusive evidence of the tunnels had been confirmed by this excavation.
The evidence presented by Stickel and his team is as follows, and this is a direct quote from Stickel's summary here.
One, an identified entrance. Two, the architecture was both linear and slightly curved.
Okay, so it gets very technical. It gets very technical.
The tunnels is like, that's one of the interesting parts of it.
There's a lot of information about this and everything, right?
It was a tragedy
They spent seven years this lady was in a wheelchair right there
But I wish I could show that one though
So there's a lot of stuff that happened, okay, so
They sent these, you know, this is called a satanic panic. Okay
It was a nightmare it was a nightmare
Bear with me bear with me
Back in the 80s and early 90s, a wave of troubling accusations swept across North America.
You and intense scrutiny on the activities of satanic cults,
stories of devil worship and satanic cults corrupting young minds,
unbelievable crime at the hands of satanic cults.
There were terrifying tales of secret satanic cults
bent on tormenting and corrupting the young.
Heavy metal music had hidden satanic messages.
Possibly satanic messages on some rock music recordings.
Games like Dungeons and Dragons were luring kids to devil worship.
And it got even stranger.
The allegations of physical and sexual abuse of children
at a babysitting service to the dark world of ritualistic child abuse.
There's a widely held opinion that what happened at the daycare
was the devil's handiwork.
Underground networks of Satanists were
infiltrating daycares and preschools to physically and sexually abused children in occult rituals.
Much of what fueled the panic was not real. These claims led to a wave of high-profile
criminal trials in the U.S., Canada, and beyond.
The cases often followed a similar pattern. An initial report of physical or sexual abuse
at a daycare would snowball, taking on a life of its own. Overzealous interveners,
everyone from parents to police to counselors would question children.
Some as young as two years old, in ways now known to produce false allegations.
Children began to talk about animal sacrifices, blood rituals, secret tunnels, even cannibalism.
Police would lay charges.
Prosecutors would take them to court and the media would report uncritically on what seemed to be a growing threat.
Authorities searched frantically for evidence of an apparent ritual abuse epidemic across North America.
Some cases would fall apart at trial or during appeal. Others resulted in wrongful convictions.
Many of the accused spent years in prison while others faced financial ruin and damaged reputations.
As it turns out, the Satanic Panic may have its origins in Canada.
When asked about the spark that set off the hellfire, many experts point to this book,
Michelle Remembers, published in 1980, written by Canadian psychiatrist Lawrence Paster and
his former patient, Michelle Smith.
The book provided a template for the allegations of satanic ritual abuse that followed.
memories from her early childhood of a terrifying initiation into a secret
cabal of Satanists operating near Victoria, British Columbia they would put
me in cages they would sacrifice animals they would have a lot of candles and
chanting and
Bizarre things I had never seen.
Did people think this was a fantasy that you'd made this all up?
It was such hocus pocus that it couldn't possibly have happened.
Well, I was one of the first to stand up and start to recount these kinds of things
and to bring it publicly.
There was no evidence or witnesses to Smith's account.
Yet, Paster presented the book as a true story.
The hard evidence is difficult to find because if a child is sacrificed, that child's body isn't going to be left.
If it's an orthodox satanic cult, they're going to burn the body and they're going to eat it during ceremonies, so they'll leave no evidence around.
Michelle remembers it was also one of the first books to suggest that underground satanic networks were not only real, but were infiltrating communities in an organized effort.
Anyone could be a satanist. They're a next-door neighbor.
dentist, or your daycare provider. It was an idea that stuck with many readers.
The book became an overnight sensation, and Pazder and Smith received a lucrative publishing deal
about $1.2 million in today's dollars. It also established Pazder as a sought-after expert
on the burgeoning phenomenon of ritual abuse.
A term he coined himself.
There was even talk of a movie deal
with Dustin Hoffman playing Pasder.
For the McMartin preschool trial
in Manhattan Beach, California,
where seven daycare workers were accused
of ritually abusing children.
Pastor was flown down to be an expert consultant in satanic cults for the prosecution.
In another ritual abuse case in Bakersfield, California, Michelle remembers was used as
training material by social workers who believed they had uncovered an extensive satanic pedophile ring.
Specialists in satanic ideology were suddenly in high demand as more and more ritual abuse cases went to trial.
In Austin, Texas, another self-styled satanic cult expert was used to secure the convictions of daycare owners Dan and Fran Keller.
who spent decades in prison before being exonerated.
It became increasingly common to see ritual crime training seminars led by psychologists,
church groups, and even the police.
This is former FBI agent Ken Lanning, who studied the spread of the panic in the 80s.
All these people network with each other and they'd all get together and goes to seminars and discussions
And they'd be told this is what Satanists do and this is how they do it
And so all that is planted through the use of these kinds of techniques hypnosis and other ways
That cause the spread of this kind of stuff
So many people say well you can't identify these cases unless you've been trained to learn about them
And some of that training becomes a self-fulfilling prophecy
The commercial success of Michelle remembers inspired dozens of copycat memoirs which further amplified the perception that satanic ritual abuse was widespread.
But there was never any evidence.
of a satanic conspiracy. In 1994, a psychologist from the University of California researched
over 12,000 accusations of ritual abuse, but found no substantiated reports of organized satanic groups
who sexually abused children. In later years, as the panic died down,
I'm not there to believe or not believe, I'm there to try and understand what they're trying to tell me of an experience.
Whether that has actually happened to them or whether that is their way of trying to express a profound pain that they've experienced.
Neither he nor Smith ever publicly renounced the book's allegations.
This strange period of moral hysteria serves as a reminder of what can happen when we abandon the pursuit of facts for a more sensational fiction.
The question is, have we learned our lesson?
I'm Lisa Brynrundle, host of Uncover Satanic Panic.
You can listen to the series now on the CBC Listen app, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Is there a well-organized plot and insidious design right now to program and influence the minds of our children towards the occult and witchcraft?
Sensationalism it kind of just reminds me of
Yeah, have we learned our lesson no we have not
Unfortunately, I wish I was just more more known about I mean see I was in preschool about this time I
This is my my area in Manhattan beaches the city next to me well, there's hermosa and then there's Manhattan
Yeah, so yeah generational forgetting well, that's why I and it's like here
I am like I don't want to be the turd in the punchbowl. Oh look, you know people are like no
Everyone people like to believe stuff too, right?
It's like I bet you can see it's people are making money from making books about it
You should see the psychiatrist that they use I think her name is Kate Griggs or something
Okay, great. Yeah, this is her. Oh, that's not her. Hold on
You see these puppets, this is not the Muppets
Let's see
And it's interesting yeah, they had this psychiatrist she used puppets
of it therapy.
I'm sorry.
I'm going so slow.
Oh, it's her name.
These puppets.
OK.
Big Martin.
OK, Bucky.
Oh, her name is Key McFarlane.
OK, so this lady is Key McFarlane,
This is who they used to interview them.
Okay.
He McFarland.
You should watch, but there's, yeah,
there's good movies about it.
Yeah, puppets.
Well, they go hey
It's part of her job she interviewed 400 children for the McMartin preschool using anatomically correct dolls and hand puppets
They they had a predetermined belief that this has happened and so that they would deny it without special techniques
Designed to encourage disclosure the interviewing techniques used during investigations of the allegations were highly suggested and invited them to pretend
or speculate about supposed events and
So then it goes to 300 it turned into one person 360 and then it says
So they would ask leaving questions repetitively, which is a set always yields positive responses
Okay, so basically if you keep interrogating interrogating interrogating
eventually just because
They know that they're not going to get anywhere until they
Give the answer they want to hear and I'm not saying that this lady knew that
She was doing this but
Yeah, they had to re-train a lot of these psychiatrists and
If you ever can come across some of these uh
those interviews
Or they actually they actually made examples of them, you know
You can see how it can see how it worked. Okay. Well, let's see what's going on in the chat
generational forgetting yeah, okay, so
Yeah, it keeps going quiet so
Maybe it's not like, you know, that interesting to people, but I find it so interesting
How this mass hysteria happens and it's like only if you're not emotionally involved
Can it make sense?
But the thing is here that there are cults there are there are
But one thing does not make something else true
Let me see what was I making here
Yeah, it's kind of going to be
Difficult to
Without interaction, I'm not sure
I probably will will uh scare a lot of people away
I just need to work on my presenting skills.
Oh, you're yawning?
Good little cat.
Okay, well, we can go on to other topics.
So, yeah.
Hi, Katrina.
Yeah.
Mr. Tricks.
Oh.
He's very, very sweet.
Oh, oh, you like when I pet your head like that?
Oh, yes.
I could be a cat in a suit, I definitely could.
You guys can hear him, just purring.
Can we hear you purr?
He's really loud.
Yeah, talking on microphone. Hey Katrina
Mmm
It's just like his last night I was I'm not going to go into like the conspiracy stuff
I was watching last night of course conspiracies that it's crediting work
but I couldn't even present the
material because the emotional reaction was so
visceral
How dare you question how dare they question even question. It's like that is not useful
It's like all you have to do is add some kind of detail that you're not you're not supposed to
Not supposed to question and that was just like and that really saw me when people go into the ether going into the ether means
It's something that's used in like like it's kind of a term
Referring to con artists con artists will get people into the ether. They'll get people to
out of their rational mind by getting them into emotions.
And they're very easy to manipulate at that time.
It's part of a con.
I mean, and I've studied a lot of the stuff.
But yeah, it's very, yeah.
There's very,
this crediting can be very, very effective.
And so I would say study maybe,
Logical fallacies
Arguments ad hominem attacks. Yeah, pretty good
Where's Mike?
Okay, Rudy's doesn't really perfectly no, do I come over here? I
Have a cool book look at this cool book. This is called a cartoon utopia
Okay
It's pretty amazing.
You can really see that well.
I want to get a turdy.
This is crazy art.
I wish I could draw that like that in detail.
And this whole book is like this, this is like a DMT kind of, I got a lot of cool books
though too.
A lot of good stuff to share, yeah.
So I'm just trying to like, what direction is this show gonna go in, like I don't know,
it's basically my entertainment, but a lot of it's not being very much fun.
so maybe we'll like
When I did have fun, I mean, let's go but let's go back in time to when I had fun on this show a lot
I mean, I do have fun with
Chat kind of but it's like, you know
It was a different kind of thing. Let's go back to in time
You can see me when I was I
Mean it looks like it was maybe ten years ago
It was only last year
Right? But I've aged 10 years from the show.
But let's see how the show used to go.
I know people will say, don't play old episode, oh my God, don't...
I'll play it with commentary.
You're interested in seeing how the show used to be.
Like the different vibe and how maybe people were different.
Let me see. I go back to my oldest lives.
okay my oldest lives when I first started doing panel I was like I was like I
want to find my first panel that I had SIG on and I met SIG for the first time
wouldn't that be interesting to find something like that okay so let's see I
started doing the open panels I want to see my first open panels so that's
A year ago. Okay, so I see I got 36 views nine views
Then I started 158 168 95 and it's already getting popular. I started getting like 300 300
Okay, so I started doing open panels that really did
Yo really did kick off the show so why is it six? Oh, yeah, because everything's private
Y'all on private some stuff
go back in time. I will have to unprivate a lot of stuff so you can enjoy. Okay.
I've done over, I think I've done like 1400 or something lives. Quite a few.
But it does take a little bit. I have 894 that I haven't deleted, I mean, so there's 894
that I've deleted probably about 500, you know, porn bombings, various stuff said that
I didn't want on, right? So, I'll just keep going back, going back October. I'm gonna
go back to maybe like, February of last year. It was so different. You'll see how different
Pretty crazy.
I'm only in July.
I'm only as fast as I can through these.
Okay, July.
I'll start.
Get to February, I'll start.
February, March, April.
Yeah, those were like these glory months of the show.
I need to remember myself having fun.
Because some people have made it not very fun for me.
Mostly you know who.
Okay.
Let's see.
I'm gonna put these all on.
Visibility public, okay, I'll do some public update.
Let's see, we'll choose one of these.
Thank you for being here, guys, by the way.
I know, and you're being very patient with me.
I appreciate that.
Okay, I'm just gonna go back to February.
So let's see, open panel.
Yeah, when it was open panel, Tarot and Cats.
Oh my God, it looks really bad there.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Let's see, how about,
let's do a one year ago today, March 12th.
This is one year ago today.
On the show.
with those enjoyers.
What?
This is before we even dance to the mystery cut.
Oh, yeah, it's the dance to the mystery cut.
Dance to the mystery, yeah, yeah, yeah So let the tarot move with the rhythm, yeah, yeah, yeah
Flow
the balance every card and open door feel the romance in every arcane lore destiny and wine
as the moon begins to soar
Second time once a year.
You already see the bus is going on with all of the droning.
To the mystery
Yeah, that happens sometimes guys. You know, part of being popular happens to all of us at the open pan.
You're Nancy. Hold on, your court case is settled. Hold on, somebody wants a reading.
We get some joker. Some joker. Some joker. Oh my god. He's way too slow.
And so... Bad thinking can get in trouble for for gorillas having sex.
It was Gorillaz having sex. See that I'm kind of it's almost kind of cringy watching me. Yeah, you want something about your court case
I'll do three cards me real quick. Your court case has been settled Nancy. Okay. Let's have a look
Now you want to know what's next for you. Hey KZ
Okay, well, it looks like things are gonna go better because you got wheel of fortune the wheel of fortune is gonna be in your favor, okay?
so it's kind of like
You've been waiting to like start over again like okay, you can finally do that because it's kind of been out of your favor, right?
You're gonna be more protected you're not quite traumatized by it, but you're
You're on guard now. You're like gonna be more careful about something
Okay, this is gonna be two, okay.
Yeah.
Feels like you were like someone did try to hurt you
through this and they just see,
I just hear like they just scratched you.
They didn't like make a flesh wound.
Are you like I I think love love is coming up for you
You can like start you can like now you can feel comfortable to go ahead
With the relationship or something it's something's been on hold
Someone's coming in for you
It's a night energy, it's not a king yet. I don't know it's like it looks like it's like maybe dating
Um, but this, yeah, just, I would just watch, just, uh, be, be careful, you know, to be
more careful now.
I don't know anything about your case or whatever, but it seems like, um, you need to be more
careful about something, protect what you have to, I see, like, there's a lot of prosperity
and stuff, a lot of, like, a lot of good, good happening, like, you.
That's really good that you settled the court case too.
I think that that put everything on hold for a while,
like a long time for you, a year or two.
Like where you couldn't move.
Now you can move and you're protected.
Just watch out who you let in your life.
You know, just be more careful.
You want to link?
Okay, be more careful, okay?
I'll put the link down below.
I am kind of embarrassed by these old episodes, because I don't feel like this was like,
I feel like I was like so innocent.
Like, you know, but maybe if there's an aunt having sex, you can get in trouble if it's two.
Let's see, do I have, oh look at my, look at the open panels get so fast, look at how, oh and Alex is there, look how fast it goes, hold on, Page is there, Alex, this is cool.
Look at the burger special, let's watch the bullshit a little bit.
They're next to her neighbor and she was-
Seymour butts, there's no Seymour butts.
Seymour butts.
I mean, everybody showed up to the chat, it was like the whole Simpsons catalog of Bart Simpson calling Moe's Tavern, it was like every name.
Hey everybody, but it's cool. I'm a Simpsons fan. Monk.
I had all these trolls. Everyone was like, see more buds.
Yeah, you're an 80s baby too. I think you're 80s baby too.
And so it's like, we, you probably remember when the first like, it was Christmas time,
and we all go back from some kind of church event. And then it was like the Simpsons premiere
episode. Yeah, my family for sure. Well, yeah, it's like, well, I wanted to go to a youth group.
And so while we would do like, um, like a recreation of like not the other
Yeah, like over there like like you've got to do this or else. Yeah.
Once you get into one demand, you're going to give into more demand.
My brother!
Hi.
Well, Psych, I got to tell you something.
Good afternoon.
Good afternoon, Howard.
I'm doing great, brother. How are you?
I'm just peachy
How are you feeling ah?
Yo psyche if I ever see your cat, I'm gonna fuck it. What the oh my god this guy
Yo, I
Can't even defend you bro. I really can't I don't like keep bringing them on I'm like I think that's some stupid
I don't know I keep bringing that guy back. I can't defend you saying I really can't like I enjoy talking to you at times
but
Lee you're too much of a liability, bro. What the fuck?
All right, let's just ignore that right let's just bring in the positive
Didn't happen you can sit backstage take for a little bit. Yeah, there you go. Just enjoy a little 24-hour timeout now backstage
I'm just doing this backstage. Yeah, that's for you right there. You scumbag. Yeah
Yeah, go do that shit on Rumble SIG. Do you know what SIG stands for?
Stands for SIG motherfucker. It stands for SIG
Incubit
Goober. They did. Okay. Good. Good, Nancy. I'm glad that I
Glad I hit pretty good. Yeah, um, I was a scumbag idiot. Yeah
Goblin, that's what that stands for
Yeah, I agree. That was a year ago. I was just looking and there's you can just see how like
different it was kind of like that, but I
Think people's true colors finally do show, you know
But hopefully I'm more of like myself, I mean, I think I I'm a lot more comfortable. I'm a lot more
I was I remember I was expressive. I was very very nice back that I was very like
la de da like
They try it again, let me let me just get this this this card for Nancy. Well, they try it again
Nancy wancy this this moon card like the moon is like yeah, it's like there's stuff, maybe
See this series he's kind of kind of concealed by the full moon like there. I think
Behind the scenes there could be stuff going on at least thoughts discussion
Illusion so just
Really like I say just protect yourself like protect yourself and
Look into some kind of security measures. Okay. You feel like you're being yeah
Yeah, you know you're being set up. Okay. I'm right. Okay good
It's like I there's what you know, you just have you know how to protect yourself
You do know how to protect yourself and it's like it's basically Nancy. I'm just seeing it's like the people
It's like the people you trust the people the people the people the people
Yep, yeah, and so be careful especially because of that night coming in that night didn't look very trustworthy
It's like just be careful who you let in because it's like that's the big part of it
It's a big part of what happened. Okay, but don't but also don't be paranoid and don't let it like
Like let it change you for the better. Let it just make you more aware. So that's for Nancy
So but anyway, yeah, you were one of the first guests in the show
I mean sick was one of the first and of course, you know
be to
That's a whole other she did say like she did say oh, are you sure you want me to promote your show?
And I was like, yeah, I thought like I mean it's like I did come out of like I
Would say
some of the IP to universe kind of energy which is like not her but it's in
the ballpark right yeah and and I didn't quite know she was so with the
bullshit as she is whatever same but hey you live and learn right you live and
And harder
Yeah, but not yeah, I don't but I don't think I do have a good heart and I
Never wanted to like I never want to like be changed so much where it's like I just like I turn into like a
Less loving person. Well, no harder. I meant like
Oh, hold on white dog pull cards for me the high priestess magician and judgment. Oh, those are interesting cards to go together
Yeah
I think but I think I'm thinking of like yeah, I'm thinking so I think with the high priestess. I'm thinking of
somebody
That's what if it was a high priestess reverse that'd be like a you know, witch
But I'm thinking like I'm gonna evil thinking that there's that that's kind of a better high priestess also like in this intuition and judgments
Maybe being called in a situation, but with that with that magic with the high priestess. That's uh, I
Know risky there brother
Little risky. Yeah, so what's up with you? What's up with what? What are you?
Why are you promoting Sam and so much like what's the deal with you and Sam and you're trying to?
Stir up the bullshit. No, I'll be honest with you and I've never told you this because I never want you to feel like
I don't take this the wrong way, all right?
Thank you, I appreciate it.
I go into other channels, I call in the stream yards.
I promote your channel and I promote Sam's channel.
Always, always, always, always.
Yeah.
I always ask, hey, is it okay if I promote this channel?
Can I plug a channel?
Yeah.
They'll tell me yes.
Thank you for promoting mine.
And I hope you haven't changed your ad
because I've been promoting Cult of Psych.
No, no, no, you're at for the channel
Yeah, oh my the name of the channel. I guess yeah, is it cult of psych together cult of psyche is the name of my channel, correct?
Oh, there you go. Yeah, that's what I was
And KULT yep, I was promoted this one here cult of psych and then I've always um
I've always promoted same ends. It's just you know at the end of the day. We're all part of one big diet been diagram
And I guess the more eyes we get, you know,
you never know who could be become a donator.
Sure, I mean, yeah, I appreciate that.
I, so I can appreciate that.
I just, I just didn't know.
They got, that guy, it was kind of weird.
I got the guy, I just saw it came in and then I didn't know.
Like, was that a joke where you're talking about
like he ate plastic and then you, you were the plastic man.
I mean, look, I'll be honest with you.
I hope he's not listening because I'm gonna feel bad.
I think, I've never met him.
I've never spoken to him before.
I do feel bad for him though.
I think he might be a little, you know, a little,
you know what I mean?
Crazy?
No, not crazy.
You know what I mean.
I don't want to say it.
Okay, but I don't know what you're talking about.
A little slower, he's me.
I think he's a little slower.
Okay.
But, you know, I did.
He seemed like a genuinely laced guy, okay? Yeah, I think he's nice you I actually know him from before
Okay, yeah in case the I it's okay. I know KZ is a mess that that's
I mean, I love what KZ was so funny when he's like I dated her 14 years ago, and he's like I was thinking of someone else
That happens everyone. I dated people 14 years ago. I never I never met or anything
The fuck
You know who Emma is
Amatil I'm a Leviathan
I'm a Leviathan. Yeah
What is that? Is that a joke? No, she um, she's a terror reader and she I was actually like a
Mod for her. She has like about 20,000 subscribers. I was a mod and like I got unceremoniously like, you know
You've mentioned her. Yes. Yeah get ready for Fred Fred Alistair to start talking
It's also Fred Levi's and he's other he always is lurking and stuff. He's gonna say don't say her name
I'm allowed to talk about her. She's a public figure, right? That's what she wants. Okay
Stop promotion
Yeah, help connecting me to her you connected yourself to her my friend Casey
I never connected you to her you said you were dating her 14 years ago and
What were you in her chat and stuff and why is he in the chat right now? Yeah, Casey is yeah
Why was I nutty enough to get you in a Lisa's discord? I hope you're not in her discord
You weren't you hurt her again, and you said sorry. Oh
But you heard her ego and you said sorry. I don't
He said he heard her ego.
I don't know, I don't know.
I want to hear more about it, Casey.
Can you come up and discuss it?
Anyways, but yeah, I'm always promoting your channel
when I go over there.
I'm always promoting Samans.
It's just, like I said, maybe, who knows?
Maybe a dollar or two could come in.
A dollar is better than nothing, you know what I mean?
Well, I mean, it's like I really don't make nothing. I mean, I have always gotten donations.
Somebody will get zero donations. I mean, I always get donations. Sometimes just recently,
you know, I used to be able to cash out every month.
You have to get like a hundred dollars in donations to cash out through YouTube, but you know, I still get cash out donations and stuff like that.
And other things, I would say, I would say I'm very blessed.
Even like, you know, Alice got me dinner last night and has gotten me dinner several times and other people have gotten me.
McQueen?
Yes, McQueen.
Oh wow, what did he get you?
He got me McDonald's, he got me three coffees and a hot honey chicken sandwich and a large
fries.
What?
Yeah.
Wow.
So, shout out to Alex, thank you very much, that was really, really good.
He's a generous dude, huh?
He's very generous, yeah.
I didn't send, did I send you to her channel?
How did I, I sent you to her channel?
Oh, hold on.
Your ego that says back her ego is Bruce. She clearly thought I remember her but you didn't
You took
I'm not sure. I'm not yeah, let's just ignore it's okay. I'm not sure
Yeah, goodbye weirdo you're gone. Bye
Anyways, so what's for dinner? What's for lunch? Did you cook anything? Did you prep anything?
I had a bagel for breakfast, and I fell asleep because I had to drink a beer too.
And then I just finished a coffee. I have another coffee. I'm a little bit, you know, a little bit down, but...
A little tired?
No, I'm tired, yeah. I'm just kind of like also...
Yeah, I'm always sexy a little bit bummed out. Yeah, I don't think you offended her
I don't mean things. I don't mean to hear on her radar really Casey. I mean, it's like, please
I mean, I was like with all due respect fuck her
Hey, Casey, you're a weirdo fuck you
So I'm gonna drink some more coffee.
Yeah, all right, here we go.
My segment of the show, welcome to the corner.
That's the new show.
Host, yours truly the number one troll in the community.
They're not selling them anymore?
You had the last white dog yet.
I like the hot honey.
Hot?
You know, I don't remember ever
they're being a hot honey, like come out,
but it's like now this year.
You know, that's like, it's like it was on McDonald's and what else that had hot honey?
Like there's another restaurant that started having hot honey on it too.
I don't know if it was Subway or...
What is going on?
Have you had it? Have you tried the hot honey?
What hot honey tea?
You know, McDonald's, that's like, they had like, that was one of the like flavors of the, of the day, or like month or whatever.
They started having like hot honey chicken wraps, hot honey on the, on the chicken sandwiches.
Oh, KFC, yeah, KFC, uh, honey, um...
What the fuck?
Uh, no, I'm kidding, come on.
I thought you were beat-a for a second.
Really?
Oh, you sound just like her.
So...
There you go again.
Where do they have...
You bet!
Sweet heave, yep.
Fuck you, bitch!
I got real friends, and I backstabbed them.
Uh, I only backstabbed my real friends bet
Now he's saying he smashed her
Okay, what what made be the one to join yesterday? Well, why?
What a weirdo, huh? I
Don't know. She and but it was going in circles. It wasn't what was it? Yeah, the question Nancy
I'll answer another question, but yeah, you have to you have to ask. I'm sorry if I missed it
I didn't I don't see it. You said oh, it's always the same thing with it
Oh, you know, why are you talking about me over here?
I have not mentioned you for a whole month.
Okay, say, for a whole month.
My country in Iran is going through horrible stuff
and you're here talking shit about me.
Fuck you.
You bet.
Yeah, yeah, it's like if you're on a batch be like B.A.T.C.H.
Yeah, BATS.
My country of Iran is much better than your country and and you're here laughing at my nose.
Fuck you, BATS.
It's like both Nancy now like you have an advantage now at this point you have an advantage like you have a like a little
Advantage over a little push. Yeah, you have an ace. It's like it was it's like an ace in your ace in your sleeve
I think like it's gonna be harder for them to get away with what they did before
Okay, I'm okay. We're not trying to confuse you. You're confusing me. You're saying you KZ
Say he now he's saying he smashed. He smashed her pussy. That's what he said. What dude
nobody that that
That gets laid says something like that.
I know, it's just disgusting.
You're not talking about my pussy!
Fuck you, Bats!
And KZ, I don't know, you're confusing me, KZ.
Fuck you, KZ, you fucking weirdo.
Fuck you, KZ. I hope I helped. I hope I helped.
I mean, yeah. And if you want to do like...
Can we reenact?
How about you, you be you and I'd be beta one second. We can do it, but Nancy
psyche at cult of psyche comm and if you want to do a
More in depth. I'll do one more card for you. If you want me to do more and that would be caught. Let's see if there's
Messages there. Well, it's like you're getting this Empress energy. It's like
Basically, that's that's that's up to you to help. Like I guess like, okay, awesome. That'd be great
Yeah, I think you're in this energy where you can you can give this more power now you're in a higher power position
It's like and you can help with this right
Yeah, you can help with the
Stop stopping it. You can help other people maybe too
Um, yeah, kasey come up on panel get up on panel kasey. We need to talk to you. Hi. Let's re-enact it. You ready? Yeah
All right, ubu. I'd be beta
Um, hi, sweetie
Hey, how are you? How are the cats? They're good. Oh, look here's Lenore and
Tricks. Oh, very nice cat. I love the cat. Yes. That's how we've been beta. Oh
Hey little pussy. Hi
That makes three of us now
Hello, yes, I get it. It's like, yes, you can put your cat down now. It's okay. Thank you
I've got my own cats and they're better than yours. Okay. Okay. Say how to make me say how to make in mini for me
I'd love your cats too. Okay. Don't there you go again. And now you go talk about my cats now
I said hi to them really you are going to start slandering my my my own cats really
That's not slander. There's just I just said hi. Hi Mickey mini listen in my country
You are not allowed to to talk or even look
At the other person nevertheless are sacred cats you understand that
Yes, okay, what's going on be that?
Well, anyway, I'm calling to tell you that I love the channel here.
You are doing great things.
You do?
I think you're a very good person and a kindhearted, kindhearted man.
Thank you.
Oh, you're awesome.
I love you too.
It's something I would tell you if I were a friend.
I don't like you.
I can't stand you.
You don't stand for anything.
What?
Yeah, yeah, you want to, yeah, yeah, in my country, we, we haven't papered like you.
I'm strangling the kiddie, kiddie, don't you understand that, Psyche?
Yeah.
Okur?
Okay, you know survive five minutes in Iran you motherfucker you I am going to get the telephone and they will
You're pretty good that is a pretty good voice
Oh, shit, dude, I cracked myself up, bro.
I hope that there's somebody out there that's laughing with me.
Somebody in the chat.
I'll be laughing.
Like, how is that not funny, bro?
I think KZ is disturbing everybody.
Yeah, let's get a man out of here.
What is the you'll see part about it?
Like, what is the you'll see?
Yeah, why are you threatening?
Yo, KZ, you got five minutes to donate or else you're banned.
Do you sweepie now? Yeah, do sweepies voice
Hey psyche, how are you? Hey?
Hey psych needs to be worked on okay. Yeah, hey, honey. How are you?
She never she never talked to me like that. Yeah, but this is me now you understand that
Okay, you know that that that one needs to go back to the workshop for a little bit, but no you need to go back to the workshop
Okay, I've lost 20 pounds
Since the last time I spoke with you psyche
Okay, well, you know, she did send me pictures like I said the pictures look like they're from I said Sears catalog
Maybe maybe JC penny catalog. Yeah, I've I've sent you photos
Those are from the past
Do you understand that?
But they're the the text that she did send me we're quite there me
This person is a little bit
Not obsessed but a little bit
I'm not obsessed with you psych not at all. I've got my own channel. I
Know but I'm isn't it all me?
Negative it's about the content of the community
Yeah
Me with like, you know bald and you know covered in trash
Yeah, well cry about it. How about that? What how you about it?
Cry about it. Yeah, I do
Well keep it up. I've got a friend
Who's from Iran? Yeah
And she's she has somebody
Who works for the Taliban?
Come on, okay, come on.
Get into...
I mean...
I mean, now I'm really gonna get in trouble.
Come on.
But that's not you, it's me.
I know, but it's like, it doesn't matter if it's you.
Like seriously, it's never me.
It's always somebody else, but then it's like I get,
I always get yelled at.
It's never, well who got this strike?
All the people, who got this strike?
Me, struck me out of everybody.
I'm like the least of her worries in this world.
I mean, really, I'm like, and then trip, trip and sip is like,
Oh, here's Psyche, like, you know, lurking outside your door and, like, fake surveillance
camera footage and shit like that.
What?
Yeah, she says, she says, oh, Edith's, Edith should sandwich and then she goes, I would
never say that.
That's what she said the other day.
I would never say that.
Yeah.
She doesn't remember dog shit.
All the fucking liquor she's drunk.
I'm going to get my little papoose.
I'll be right back.
Hold on.
Give me one second.
Okay.
Oh
I mean the thing is it's like I really don't even have anything against her, but then she's like so mean to me
You know and it's like and then some of it's like and then it's like
then she'll like kind of like
Pretend to be nice, right?
She did she has said many times she doesn't okay. She doesn't drink
What is the whole on Lisa be acting like she don't like me when I go in her chat
Leave be ignoring me. What the fuck happened? Well, I don't think she does like you
You were weird. Did she kick you out of the discord yet? Okay, hold on Sam
Dropping it
Hold on a second.
It takes me a second.
A bit slow.
Here we go.
We've got to make sure he's oiled up.
Ew.
KZ.
Yo.
Yo, what's up?
What's the beef now?
Why can't we?
What's up?
I have no beef.
Yeah, y'all here talking about beat again.
Oh, shut up.
What?
What happened?
Well, now you can about be the since when now
What is asking because the Arthur?
I'm just having a conversation with Arthur. I can't control what he comes out of his mouth. I'm just saying I'm just
Why you get him mad? Why you get him mad?
I thought you had no beef. I don't know what happened. I have no beef at all. Yeah, you talk your shit
What is the two days now?
Huh
Huh two days now. What happened? I'm not even talking shit. It's always Arthur. Yeah
Arthur's repeat niggas. That's a sweet piece after be the what happened kitty gang. What happened?
Nothing what
Yeah, now y'all go quiet now see talk to me. No, we'll talk and be this voice
What are you trying to play me nigga
I'm really jealous. I'm I'm
actually so jealous and I'm
actually green with envy. I
wish I was I wish I was her.
I wish I was her.
That's a sweet pea. Yeah
You got that
There's a dig sucker Arthur watch. I'm telling you Arthur's a fucking dig sucker and I go what?
attention
Hey, man suck it from the back. He does it right Arthur sucker from the back. That was a request
I'm just kidding. Oh shit. Yeah. Yeah. Hope that shit dropped nigga. You're stupid bitch
Hey, what?
You don't talk to me like that and word you talk to me how you try to put your your gay advances on me nigga
Over the by voice
You look like kind of like hold on what do you look like you look like Rat King?
You see KZ, KZ you look like Ratkin, you see KZ, how you look like?
It's better than saying I look like the Ratkin, so I do appreciate it.
He does look like the Ratkin. I've seen him, yeah.
From Ninja Turtles. Ratkin from Ninja Turtles, nigga.
Yeah.
KZ is a fucking word, though.
You know the Ninja Turtle character that was, is like a brain with like, you know, a moustache?
Yeah.
That's my favorite one.
Fuck, what's his name?
He has a...
Kank.
Yeah, it was a cane. Okay. Yeah same it. I saw a great a
Great something with you in it. I'm a fan of your view now. I don't know if you I'm sure you've seen it
Like you know being gay shut to be the leave it alone. I'll shut
That's Arthur faggots thinking I take it up the butt. Oh, please the language. What is wrong with you?
You fucking weirdo you fuck you out to watch what watch when I cook your eyes you a lame-ass nigga
You you guys are the ones comparing me to him they got never said
You just suckin psych dick nigga
Nobody fucking likes your channel, Doug. Nobody likes your channel. Yeah, okay. I'll go remember that you fucking dick sucker. Oh my god
Shout out to shout out to the player one
Yo
This is scary
Why is it that you're so cool saying that F word on other people's channels, but on your channel, you don't say it?
I'm making the advances on me.
Nah dude, see this is what I'm saying, like, this is the hypocrisy, like, he would get mad if somebody says that F word on his channel.
He has to do it, he has to do it, you stupid nigga, shut the fuck up.
It's why he says it too loosely over here, bro. I'd knock the shit out of him. I see him in real life
Sam and Arthur's over here promoting you 24-7. What are you doing?
Yeah, I'm always promoting you.
Fuck outta here. I don't need him to promote
That's a kitty gang. Fuck y'all lame ass niggas.
Okay, well
Yeah, y'all all y'all do is to talk that bullshit
Beed up, beed up, beed up, beed up, beed up, beed up, just like clumsy
Um, have you ever watched your show?
He doesn't even watch it in the morning. Oh, she doesn't talk about me. No, she don't. Yes. She does. No, she don't
No
That's sound like Katie
Simon you understand
That's she talks about psyche and she turns off DVR. So you don't rewind and record
Rumble everything's on record all you want stupid everything's on rumble
We have but nobody's like we're not like, you know surveillance experts like you say man
We're not sitting around. Yeah, don't fuck up reporting every show and go watch that
Hey, you watch my ass. Yeah, that's kind of why you pre-record streams. That's kind of weird
How do you pre-record strings, which is what the fuck you sit there with like a DVR recording everyone? Yeah, you're kind of weird
That's not pre-recorded strings Arthur. Yeah, you're kind of weird. That's a little weirdo action
Coming from a cooker with a PDF, right?
That's that New York weirdo type shit. You're the biggest weirdo over here. That's why you really was like, yeah
But you hear that psyche
Yeah
You dig sucker or Dominican what what you say you dig sucker you Puerto Rican Dominican or no what you say you got two dig suckers
I want to do a double hook with you guys like this. Whoa
I'm out of here. I can't tell you. Yeah, you're too gay. Yeah, I think you want to do it the hockey way
You know what I mean? I wanted you like I want to be the lead be the
Fuck you and be the fuck you too nigga. Fuck you Ron, bro
Fuck you in Venezuela a little whopper the venice. Yo chill my nigga chill the fuck. Yeah, you Colombian fake bitch nigga
You're a dick sucker for real
And you wish you do what the cat say what the fuck you doing to come out of here. What?
You wish you could suck this dick nigga
Look you suck a psych dick all day
You can't again. Fuck you bitch ass nigga challenge to the three-piece. That's a kitty gang. That's a beta
Bitch has thank you dick sucker watch this shit will be two dollars to be clout watch you can be tight
Yeah, your channel about to be clout about that
The word
Are you laughing that's what you're saying
It's a joke, bro. Jesus. All right. Say no more. Oh my god. Here we go. Say no more. Nah, you said it. It's a joke nigga
Don't move on now. You said it. All right. So if I say you're gonna take my word. All right. How about this?
I'm a millionaire. You take my word. Nah, you good. Don't threaten me. Oh my god. Here we go. I'm out of here
But yeah, you can't take a joke, bro. Yeah, don't cry now
Now they're gonna claim that you take down a channel psyche here we go
They're gonna blame you now though
This dude soft as hell bro
Make one joke. Oh my god. Oh really? Really? Oh, okay. Like Jesus
Yeah, I mean, it's like I'm against that but he already has a strike by from Alexandra
So I'm not gonna use like a little bit just like me. I don't even I'll be honest way way back then
But I've been on YouTube for a while way back then
Like my real hardcore trolling days
I used to, like, flag channels, and then I realized that shit does nothing.
So I stopped.
It really doesn't.
I mean, it doesn't do anything.
So I don't know what happened to her channel.
I've never heard...
She's like, oh, I didn't delete my own channel.
Okay, well, I'm not saying you necessarily did.
I'm saying that there's something maybe beyond...
Um, you got flagged or something like that. I don't know. It's if the channel disappears
I've never heard of that ever happening because I've had my channel taken down several times. I've had I've been flagged
I've been all this stuff and it's like it's never just like disappear. It's like, you know, it's always been like a message about
Oh, we'll remove for a community guidelines violation blah blah
It disappears, I don't know.
No, like, I've, like, before I joined any of these panels here,
any, any, any panels, any and all panels here,
I used to, like, report flagship at the other community
and nothing ever came from it.
All it ever said was,
thank you, YouTube will take this into consideration
and, like, nothing ever happened.
And the guy would say some outlandish shit on the streams, he would threaten people,
dox people, and he would leave the streams up and then we will like report it, bro, nothing
would ever be done.
I think maybe it has to do with like how big people's channels are, or like how, you know,
I'm not sure exactly.
It's not even that big.
Well, at the time it wasn't that big.
I don't even know if you're still around, but there's a channel that's kind of big and it reports like
Like a channel that's like not like an unmonitized small channel and stuff. Okay. I got you
maybe
But yeah, like like I like even if I wanted to like to me it's just so useless that I don't
I don't find any point in reporting
Especially if it's if it's channels that we get content out of like why
Do that like I'm literally just ruining it for myself, right?
So I didn't get me you get my ideology. Yeah, I
Don't know. It's like it's not like it's like she has another channel. She has
Plenty of people on it. I mean it's like everybody that she's on beat is every night promoting and so
Yeah, yeah, I'll be right back or is that cool with you you still gonna be live
That's fine. I might I might end it. It's like go to bed. I'm asleep tomorrow. Oh my god. Thanks a lot Samus. See what you fucking did
Yeah, well actually I'm gonna play this old panel with with that with her on it and stuff like that
Yeah, it's not making it on my show. I'm just kidding. Yeah, I will help I'll play and I'll be here. Okay
You guys listen joy
Classic psyche, right?
I'll try not to fall asleep
I'm just a little bit tired
Then they'll like try to threaten you and like see if you're scared and stuff
Something show no fear. Like I'm not afraid of these people. I'm not gonna do anything against my will
I'm not gonna write community posts against my will
I'll write community posts all day about my friends and how I love them and stuff
I'm not gonna like do what you want me to do like write me that it's like there's telling us
Only that my love not only that I'm not gonna
Hey, get on. I'm not going to, um, you know, that's okay. So my dad always told me if you see
somebody coming up to you on the street or I'm not going to say homeless because homeless people
are, you know, not always crazy, but what are you going to do?
You're going to stand there and argue.
No, you're going to walk away, right?
So you've got to fucking just be like, you know,
when people are trying you know, and try to dox you and say,
I'm going to come to you.
All right, I'm going to give it to you, motherfucker.
Do it.
Like, listen, Alex.
You know how many people have said that to me and I tell them,
I fucking dare you to come to my house.
I will blow your fucking head off.
Alex.
The thing about like art of war is that you've got to do things silently.
You always got to do things silently.
So you can like, we'll take the homeless situation, right?
You go, you don't argue with the homeless, you don't, you might get stabbed, you don't
want to like, you know, it's just, you don't know what they're going to, you go and you
report and you say whatever, but you know, you're not going to find that, you do what
you got to do.
She's so cute.
I'm trying to get on.
I will have to.
Don't let it get on.
Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get on. Let's get
to the kids.
Alex, your egg, what do they call that egg?
Like, what do they call it?
No, I don't think that you blend eggs with to make pancakes.
The ninja, a whisk.
A blender, a whisk.
What the fuck dude just turned into jeopardy all of a sudden.
I think your side got it wrong with-
Pardon me
Imagine you're in page together in a hotel room and just me
I can't say
Alex I'm slightly your girl, but so many for birthdays and blackout nights the triple B threat. That's it. That's all
Okay, so imagine Psyche. Okay, let's do like a skit scenario. Okay? Alex and Psyche are
lovers. Alex wants to hold a secret, but Psyche is willing to come out about it. He's an honest,
open person.
Psyche, I'm saying nothing. Don't roam out at the table.
Oliver is my Oliver and I are also kind of talking, but he's really interested in page. Okay. What's that?
Jesus
Oh, my God, psyche. What are you doing? Why is he on his? What is Alex on his knees right now? I'm a judgment
No, but you just started a triangle from out. I love trying from out. So
Alex you've been flirting with page and all along you've been fucking on your knees for fucking psyche. Yes. Yes, I have
Okay, I'm busted. But baby, the truth is disgusting. You said to us that you like me
like psyche as a friend. So I love him. I love him as a friend. We were peeping me and
Oh my God, do you know how I would do to you on page 69?
I would give almost my right arm for possession.
After Allison and I fuck, and he fucks me so hard, and then we're going to go and beat
it and Page's room, and we're going to be videotaping.
Oh my God.
I would have never known.
I had a crush on you when I was looking at you getting your freaking SUV BMW, and you
were like driving around.
I thought you were freaking straight, and then I saw this guy come in, and then he said,
You walked in together into your apartment and then I heard you say Alex come in come on my panel
Alexander and my PD act like you're straight
Yeah
Don't don't make you really live it the nightmare. We're talking about pages room now. I'm going to dream come true
And then your room is up next baby
Okay, guys and Alex Alex is about him guys. He's a couple power bottom. He likes it like for hours
I hear his love.
I know.
I saw him on the bus.
A hundred percent.
He was watching him rail here with his in the U.S.
Oh, sweaty.
You know what I like to say?
I like when I'm fucking here.
He and Paige we videoed it.
We have actual footage, guys.
I like when I'm on top of tight fucking him.
And I'm so sweaty and he's sweaty that my sweat
is dripping into his eyeballs and his hair.
It looks like he just came out of the shower.
And I'm just fucking the shit out of him.
while you engage in a particular thing and then you guys come in and join us.
Let's have some fun, ladies and gentlemen.
So basically what I'm getting is we got to buy a castle in upstate New York
before we die soon and have some fun.
You come buy a castle, look it up.
It's like a million or two, but it can be done.
Okay. If this is what you need, Vita, I'm ending this.
No, no, Oliver, what were you doing the whole time while we were fucking like...
No, I still...
No, like, you know what you were doing?
Oliver, what were you doing, Oliver?
Oliver, what were you doing?
He was checking out the page.
He was peeping out, he was like looking at the page the whole time.
He's watching me watch them.
Vita, what's it like to be totally on page?
Oliver just close your eyes close your eyes over your mouth. You'll get a big surprise. Oh, why aren't we movie producers like what?
She thinks I like Paige if I was jealous of Paige
Why would I fucking like bring her into the scenario that you were in?
And I said
Neighbor I'm jealous of her. Why do you have to bring it on the panel? That's the
God, I wish I was my age.
I know, don't tell her.
Stop, that's really mean.
I like it.
I like that this is going.
Oh, I understand, I'm just trying to get out of here.
You're hurting my feelings.
You know, hug me.
You know, this is Oliver coming to pick you up.
Is he the male man?
Is he the hot male man?
That's a little male every day, huh?
Yeah, I'm a little male man.
Have the male man, the cops are gonna come.
I think I'm a male man.
the top. You just have a glass apartment. Everybody can watch your
eyes. Yeah. Yeah, I have no friends. I have all stuck to
your fucking glass window. Watch it get reeled.
Pull the lawyer. Pull the lawyer. The whole neighborhood would be
freeing up their phone on your part. Pardon me.
Pardon me? Oh, don't try to be all nice. Pardon me?
I don't have a family, the other one.
You can't get shit.
Keeper by the dozen?
No family.
No Brady Bunch.
Oh, Brady Bunch.
Oh, we brought that up last night.
It's so funny.
Yeah, it's a story of my name and Brady.
Yeah.
Okay.
He's going to the game.
You ready?
I was going to look for my audience.
Okay.
It says my audience.
It says male 56% female 44% and it says they're from the countries
I can find the country's geography home. It says US Canada, UK, Australia, Ireland, Portugal,
Philippines, Malaysia, and Fiji
Guys, I'm being on Fiji Ireland.
Don't forget to subscribe us for more.
And count your-
Payton Albedo
And what was that one person from Fiji? Fiji gang. Yeah. Fiji gang. I'll look at my last, like, I'll look at my last, like, year.
I met people on that on con.
So in the last, in the last year, I think it's Fiji is that ping pong guy.
Yeah.
Ping pong.
It might be.
But it says US, Canada, UK, India, Australia, Turkey, Philippines, Indonesia, Ireland,
and Germany.
My countries.
That's great.
Wow.
That means that people in all those countries watching you.
He got cold in different area, cold, cold, cold, in different area, cold, cold, cold,
cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold,
cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold, cold,
Aw, we love you Timnick.
Oh, kitty gang, I love that kitty.
Mwah, Timnick.
Timnick.
Yeah.
Oh, Bunny can be cute like a bunny,
not like a cute in a sexual way.
Hey, don't listen to Nick.
Nick is adored.
Yeah, I agree with that.
It can be funny.
It can be sexual.
Or within your budget, if you want.
I like that name, by the way.
Oh, it's Lula.
What do you mean by Lula?
It's an overgave, too.
Dancing queen.
I mean, all of us are by-curious.
I think you're by-curious.
I'm bi-ready, I'm ready to go bi-
I'm bi-ready
He said I need things on my tattoos
Oh shit
I still think so
I never had little scissors in my life.
Domino's Pizza Hut and Papa John's.
You're not missing a thing.
It's like cardboard with cheese on it.
What is it?
It's like the rest of them.
Oh, your pizza and your pizza is a red good dough
and like a really lot of cheese on them.
And the California pizzas, they've got goat cheese
and like roasted peppers and like hardly any sauce.
They're still good cheese.
No, but I'll be talking about pizza and our dick.
No, no, no, no.
if somebody like sincerely makes a business inquiry for me instead of like
scaring them away like can you like say you can ask psyche when he wakes up or I don't know
I mean jeez
Thank you. Pay attention Alexander just ratted himself out like the NYPD. He is
You made a great point
New York and eating Papa John's and fucking Domino's
You're gonna tell
Yeah, you don't even get an option. Don't even look at it. Don't even look at the procedure.
I get arrested and then I go into a room and you take my anus for contraband. So tell me
until you go like prison prison.
When you're going to send your boat in, I'm going to give him his ride, tell him to bend over like a finger, like, go, it's my fantasy.
Can we do an add-on guys, you'll like it.
You want it, you want it from the top.
Alex just tell me just tell me I go in the room and I have my boxers and you're like bend over
Assume the position buddy and read me college when I'm fucking you. That's what I want. I'm gonna fuck you while you give me a reading
Like, oh my God, all these kids are panicles, the six are panicles, all I want is panicles.
No wonder I'm creepin'. That sounds hot.
But actually, like, I'd rather watch these gay guys make fun of them than fucking women.
Can you wear a screen mask and break into our home and fucking tie us both? Yeah, 100% we can play we can role play
That's my little name. Seriously. I'm gonna marry the guy who will break into
Wow
That's what we used to talk. I didn't quite know it was so gay
um
It was kind of crazy
What the fuck because we used to talk about sex the whole time like all of us having sex
Weird
Okay, wow. Um, I'm gonna show you something I found today look what I found
Something really cool
There's my history you see hold on a second
Okay, this guy's
Well, it's on it now. Nothing works. Come on open. Oh my god, it's frozen. Oh, here we go
We did this guys look what I found
coolest UIs that I've ever had the pleasure of testing.
Today, my friends, we're talking about the Biscuit Pro
by Biscuit Shop, an educational Wi-Fi auditing tool,
which is honestly one of the coolest pen testing gadgets
that I have ever had the pleasure of owning.
Hi, I'm your pal Cal, and this thing is one of the coolest
things that I've ever seen.
This device was developed by Hedge over at Biscuit Shop.
He had a full video, if you wanna see the video,
Cinema to say the least and it's down below in the description. It's got an ESP 32 room a 32 and an ESP 32 C 5
dual band Wi-Fi dual ESP 32's and
Just the amount of features this little guy has is phenomenal
It fits literally in your pocket and this is
Man, it's not something that I can just say, hey, it's in my everyday carry.
It's on my everyday person.
I love this thing, and I know I'm going to be glazing hedge this entire video, but he
deserves it, man.
This is ingenious.
Now, I'm going to fill you guys in on-
I'm kind of down today, so I'll see what I can do later, but thanks for joining me.
Have a nice day.